Guide to the Annina Nosei Gallery Archive 1963-2009 MSS.298
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Artist Files, 1963-2004
  - Subseries A: General Artist Files
    - Massimo Kaufman, 1989-1992 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Bernd Koberling [1], 1981-2005 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Bernd Koberling [2], 2002 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Joseph Kosuth, 1977-1989 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - [Kocheisen + Hullmann], undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Jeff Koons, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Barbara Kruger Announcements, 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Barbara Kruger - Correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Barbara Kruger - Press, 1983-1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Barbara Kruger, 1983-1987 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Kocheisen + Hullman, 1993-1999 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - [Material from Front Pocket of "Barbara Kruger [Binder 1]"], 1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Barbara Kruger [Binder 1] [1/2], 1985, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Barbara Kruger [Binder 1] [2/2], undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - [Material from Back Pocket of "Barbara Kruger [Binder 1]"], 1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - [Material from Front Pocket of "Barbara Kruger [Binder 2]"], undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Barbara Kruger [Binder 2] [1/2], 1985 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Barbara Kruger [Binder 2] [2/2], undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - [Material from Back Pocket of "Barbara Kruger [Binder 2]"], undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Kruger [1/3], 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Kruger [2/3], 1985,1986 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Kruger [3/3], 1986, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Guillermo Kuitca Catalogue, 1992, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Guillermo Kuitca Financial Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Guillermo Kuitca: Press, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Kuitca Press, 1990, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Guillermo Kuitca: Correspondence, 1989-1994 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Guillermo Kuitca, 1990-1994 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Gary Lang [1] [1/2], 1984-1993 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Gary Lang [1] [2/2], 1988-1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - [L], 1980-2005 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Gary Lang [2], 1988-1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Martin Larralde, 1994-2000 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Sol Lewitt, 1979-1983, 1995, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - [Gernot Linder Correspondence], 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - [Gernot] Linder, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Alfredo Londaibere, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Robert Longo, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Mark Luyten, 1992-1994 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - M, 1978-1993 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Alan McCollum [1], 1987-1993 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Alan McCollum [2], 1985-1989 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Hanging Instructions for Allan McCollum "200 Plastic Surrogates", 1993 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Kim McConnel, 1992-2001 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Robert Mangold, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - E. Mattacci - Press Catalogues, 1988-1993 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Brenda Miller, 1973, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Paul Miller, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Keith Miller, 1980-1991 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Helmut Middendorf - Corresp., 1984-1998 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Helmut Middendorf [1], 1986-2002 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Helmut Middendorf [2] [1/2], 1984-1999 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Helmut Middendorf [2] [2/2], 1984-1999 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Sabina Mirri [1], 1982-1985 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Sabina Mirri [2], 1985 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Andy Moses, 1986, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Olivier Mosset, 1981-1986 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Stephen Mueller [1] [1/2], 1984-1998 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Stephen Mueller [1] [2/2], 1994-1998 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Stephen Mueller Corresp. [1/2], 1984-1998 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Stephen Mueller Corresp. [2/2], 1982-1992 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Stephen Mueller [2] [1/2], 1984-1994 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Stephen Mueller [2] [2/2], 1986-1994 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - [Shirin Neshat - Announcements], 1996-2000 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Shirin Neshat Reviews [1/2], 1993-1997 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Shirin Neshat Reviews [2/2], undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Neshat: Correspondence with Collectors; Loan agreements for 10th Sydney [1/2], 1996 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Neshat: Correspondence with Collectors; Loan agreements for 10th Sydney [2/2], 1996 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Shirin Neshat; Show Cards, Bio, Correspondence, 1995-2000 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Shirin Neshat; Show Cards, Bio, Correspondence [2/2], 1995-1997 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Guillermo Kuitca at Sperone; Rome, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Peter Nagy, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Donald Newman [1], 1979-1991 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Donald Newman [2], 2002, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Nunzio [1], 1985-1991 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Nunzio [2], 1989 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - O, 1982-1988 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Mary Obering [1], 1988 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Mary Obering [2], 1987-1992 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Ocampo Press, 1995, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Manuel Ocampo [1/2], 1993-1997 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Manuel Ocampo [2/2], 1987-1996 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Ocampo, 1993-1998 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Athos Ongaro, 1983-1986 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Ongaro, 1988-1996 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Luigi Ontani, 1982-1992 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - P/Q, 1976-1992 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - San Lorenzo Artists, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Anna Paparatti, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Mimmo Paladino, 1979-1998 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Mimmo Paladino - Press, 1980-1983 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Perry, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Claudio Palmieri [1], 1986-1989 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Claudio Palmieri [2], 1986 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Maurizio Pellegrin, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Cristiano Pintaldi, 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Lucio Pozzi, 1979,1982 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Ramsden, 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Robert Rauschenberg, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Robilant, 1998-2001 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - R, 1976-1994 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Gert Rappenecker, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Rammellzee, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Judy Rifka, 1977, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Christiane Richter, 1991, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Ira Richer - Correspond., 1983-1987 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Niguel Angel Rios - Press, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Daniele Robbiani, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - [Loose Photographs], undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Robert Ryman, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - S [1/2], 1978-1994 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - S [2/2], 1976-1993 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - David Salle - Photos, undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - David Salle, 1979-1983 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Andrea Salvino, 1998, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Suzanne Santoro [1/2], 1973-1981 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Suzanne Santoro [2/2], undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Salomé [Folder from "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box] [1], 1981-1983 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Salomé [Folder from "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box] [2], 1981-1983 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - [Loose Material from "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box], 1982, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - [Geile Tiere Berlin], 1980 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      Format: Phonograph records. [10-inch]
      Taken from folder labeled "[Loose Material from "Salomé + Castelli Letter Box]" (Box 31, Folder 29) in series III, subseries A. Moved to separate box for preservation.
    - A [From "Salomé+ Castelli" Letter Box] [1/3], 1981, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - A [From "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box] [2/3], 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - A [From "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box] [3/3], 1981 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Cheri Samba [1], 1990-1997 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Cheri Samba [2], 1990-2002 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Salvatore Scarpitta, 1990-1992 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Mario Schifano, 1982, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Julian Schnabel, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Robert Smithson, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - [Teresa Serrano], 1994 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Teresa Serrano [1], 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Teresa Serrano [2], 1994-1998 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - [Amy Sillman], 1994 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Pablo Siquier, 1996-1998 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Frank Stella, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Randy Stevens, 1980-1992 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - T, 1981-1993 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box] [1/5] [Material from Folder "Ernesto Tatafiore], 1980-1983 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box] [2/5], 1982, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box] [3/5], 1981, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box] [4/5], 1980-1982 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box] [5/5], undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Deborah Turbeville, 1997, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Marco Tirelli [1], 1984-1992 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Marco Tirelli [2], undated (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Cy Twombly, 1977-1986 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - V/W, 1973-1994 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Adriana Varejao [1], 1995 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Adriana Varejao [2], 1994, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Jeff Wall, 1983-1987 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Sokhi Wagner, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Jenny Watson [1], 1990-1999 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Jenny Watson [2] [1/2], 1977-1999 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Jenny Watson [2] [2/2], 1991-1999 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - James Welling, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Tod Wizon - Press + Corresp., 1977-1987 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Tom Wudl, 1980-1987 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - X/Y/Z, 1977-1992 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: Master Slides Binders
    This subseries originally consisted of four large binders labeled "Master Slides A-C," "Master Slides C-G," "Master Slides H-M," "Master Slides M-O," and "Master Slides P-Z." This original arrangement has been preserved while the slides were transferred to new, archivally sound sleeves and rehoused in acid-free binders. The material in the binders is divided by tabbed dividers arranged by artists' names.
    Subseries comprises master slides kept by the Annina Nosei Gallery.
    - Master Slides A-C [1/2], undated (Album A)
    - Master Slides A-C [2/2], undated (Album B)
    - Master Slides C-G [1/2], undated (Album C)
    - Master Slides C-G [2/2], undated (Album D)
    - Master Slides H-M [1/2], undated (Album E)
    - Master Slides H-M [2/2], undated (Album F)
    - Master Slides M-O, undated (Album G)
    - Master Slides P-Z [1/2], undated (Album H)
    - Master Slides P-Z [2/2], undated (Album I)
  - Subseries C: Visuals Binders
    This subseries originally comprised one binder per artist. This original arrangement has been preserved while the visual materials were transferred to new, archivally sound sleeves and rehoused in acid-free binders.
    The original binder labels have been reproduced here, except for what appears between brackets ("[ ]"), such information was provided by the archivist for ease of use.
    Some transparencies were originally sleeved in mylar, labeled, and placed in one of eight numbered pockets in a single mylar sleeve. For preservation reasons, the original sleeve was discarded. The transparencies are placed in archivally sound plastic sleeves, and a note is included that reproduces the original numbering, usually in the form, "From Binder Sleeve Pocket Numbered 'x.'"
    Many of the original sleeves in the binders contained several [elements]. Each [element] has been separated out, placed in its own sleeve, and placed in a new binder following a cover sheet giving the original binder sleeve's order (e.g., Binder Sleeve 2/7), the series and subseries, and the name of the artist as it appeared on the original binder.
    When an original sleeve or binder pocket contained a large majority of paper-based [elements], everything in that sleeve or pocket was removed and placed in a folder that can be found in ["Subseries D: Material Separated"].
    If the original sleeve or pocket contained a large amount of photographic material as well as paper-based material, then the paper material is removed to a folder labelled with the binder's name followed by the phrase "From Binder Sleeve x/y," and the photographic material is resleeved and arranged as described above.
    In some cases, a binder sleeve with four pockets will contain four or more 3"x5" transparencies in plastic sleeves with a card or sticker taped to the sleeve giving the piece's name and dimensions. Each individually sleeved transparency is taken out of its sleeve and placed in an archival three-pocket mylar sleeve. The original plastic sleeve, if it has bears notations, is placed in the same sleeve as the transparency, along with the card or sticker that bears infomation on the artwork pictured.
    The entire contents of [Izumi Chiaraluce Binder] have been moved to Series III, Subseries E, and will not appear in Series III, Subseries C.
    Series comprises visual materials (photographic prints, transparencies, slides, negatives, etc.) and other promotional material (including artists' bios and price lists) accumulated by the Annina Nosei Gallery.
    - Ghada Amer, undated (Album J)
    - Karel Appel; Francois Boisrond; Georges Rousse, undated (Album K)
    - Argentina; Fabian Burgos; Pablo Siquier; Martin Larralde, undated (Album L)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow, undated (Album M)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [1/2], undated (Album N)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [2/2], undated (Album O)
    - Fabian Burgos, undated (Album P)
    - Pizzi Cannella, undated (Album Q)
    - Chuck Connelly, undated (Album R)
    - Fernando Canovas, undated (Album S)
    - Ceccobelli; Chia; Commandeur; Colombo, undated (Album T)
    - [Arturo Duclos], undated (Album U)
    - Arturo Elizondo, undated (Album V)
    - Pietro Fortuna, Tomarchio Levi, Ronald Gault Jirado, undated (Album W)
    - [Julio] Galan [1/2], undated (Album X)
    - [Julio] Galan [2/2], undated (Album Y)
    - [Julio] Galan New [1/2], undated (Album Z)
    - [Julio] Galan New [2/2], undated (Album AA)
    - Daniele Galliano, undated (Album AB)
    - Vincent Gallo, undated (Album AC)
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2], undated (Album AD)
    - Tsibi Geva [2/2], undated (Album AE)
    - Graciela Hasper, undated (Album AF)
    - K.H. Hodicke, Koberling, undated (Album AG)
    - [Guillermo] Kuitca [1], undated (Album AH)
    - [Guillermo] Kuitca [2], undated (Album AI)
    - Helmut Middendorf, undated (Album AJ)
    - Paul D. Miller, Gian Marco Montesano, undated (Album AK)
    - Sabina Mirri, Schifano, undated (Album AL)
    - Stephen Mueller, undated (Album AM)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides; Shirin Neshat Inventory, undated (Album AN)
    - Donald Newman [1/2], undated (Album AO)
    - Donald Newman [2/2], undated (Album AP)
    - Nunzio, undated (Album AQ)
    - Mary Oberling, Beth Brenner, undated (Album AR)
    - Manuel Ocampo, undated (Album AS)
    - Palmieri Paladino [1/2], undated (Album AT)
    - Palmieri Paladino [2/2], undated (Album AU)
    - Liliana Porter, undated (Album AV)
    - Sy Ross; Tod Wizon; Ira Richer, undated (Album AW)
    - Salomé; Castelli, undated (Album AX)
    - Cheri Samba, undated (Album AY)
    - Teresa Serrano, undated (Album AZ)
    - Marco Tirelli; Flechemuller, undated (Album BA)
    - Jenny Watson, undated (Album BB)
  - Subseries D: Material Separated from Master Slides Binders
    Series comprises mostly photographic prints and transparencies, with some slides, polaroids, and paper materials, used to inventory and promote works sold through Annina Nosei Gallery.
    The order of folders in this subseries follows the order of binders in Series III, Subseries B. Artists' names in folder titles below that appear in brackets (e.g., "[From "Jose Bedia"]")were taken from the tabbed dividers that originally organized the material in the binders.
    - Master Slides A-C [From "Jose Bedia"] [1/3], undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Master Slides A-C [From "Jose Bedia"] [2/3], undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Master Slides A-C [From "Jose Bedia"] [3/3], undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Master Slides A-C [From "Mike Bidlo;" Alighiero Boetti"], undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Master Slides C-G ["Abraham David Christian"], undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Master Slides C-G [Back Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Master Slides H-M [Front Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Master Slides M-O ["Allan McCollum"], undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Master Slides M-O [From "Stephen Mueller"], undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Master Slides M-O [Back Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Subseries E: Material Separated from Visuals Binders
    Subseries comprises material separated from Series III, Subseries C, due to some aspect of the material that made it unsuitable to be placed in a binder.
    The order of folders in this subseries follows the order of binders in Series III, Subseries C. Each folder represents one binder sleeve; for example, when all the material has been removed from the ninth sleeve of the "Pizzi Cannella" binder in Subseries C, it is placed in a folder, which is then labeled "Pizzi Cannella [Binder Sleeve 9/12]." When only some of the material is removed from a sleeve, it is noted in the folder title as "[From Binder Sleeve x]" (e.g., Pizzi Cannella [From Binder Sleeve 4/12]").
    General Note
    The folder labeled "[Izumi Chiaraluce Binder]" contains the entirety of the binder since it is mostly paper material.
    - Ghada Amer [Front Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Ghada Amer [Binder Sleeve 1/2], undated (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Ghada Amer [Back Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Karl Appel; Francois Boisrond; Georges Rousse [Front Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Karl Appel; Francois Boisrond; Georges Rousse [From Binder Sleeve 1], undated (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Karl Appel; Francois Boisrond; Georges Rousse [Back Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Argentina; Fabian Burgos; Pablo Siquier; Martin Larralde [Front Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Argentina; Fabian Burgos; Pablo Siquier; Martin Larralde [Binder Sleeve 7/13], undated (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Argentina; Fabian Burgos; Pablo Siquier; Martin Larralde [Back Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [Front Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 11/13], undated (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 12/13], undated (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 13/13], undated (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [Front Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [From Binder Sleeve 1/21], undated (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [From Binder Sleeve 7/21], undated (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [From Binder Sleeve 13/21], undated (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [From Binder Sleeve 14/21], undated (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [Back Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Fabian Burgos [Binder Sleeve 2/12], undated (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Fabian Burgos [Binder Sleeve 3/12], undated (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Fabian Burgos [Binder Sleeve 12/12], undated (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Pizzi Cannella [Front Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Pizzi Cannella [From Binder Sleeve 1/12], undated (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Pizzi Cannella [From Binder Sleeve 4/12], undated (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Pizzi Cannella [Binder Sleeve 9/12], undated (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Pizzi Cannella [Back Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Fernando Canovas [Front Pocket], undated (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 2/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Fernando Canovas [Binder Sleeve 3/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Fernando Canovas [Binder Sleeve 4/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Fernando Canovas [Binder Sleeve 5/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 17/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 18/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 19/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 20/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Fernando Canovas [Binder Sleeve 21/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 22/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 23/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Fernando Canovas [Binder Sleeve 24/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 25/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 27/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 28/28], undated (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Fernando Canovas [Loose Material] [1/5], undated (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Fernando Canovas [Loose Material] [2/5], undated (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Fernando Canovas [Loose Material] [3/5], undated (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Fernando Canovas [Loose Material] [4/5], undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Fernando Canovas [Loose Material] [5/5] [Unlabeled Folder], undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - [Izumi Chiaraluce Binder], undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Entire contents of binder. See General Note, above.
    - Chuck Connelly [Front Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Chuck Connelly [From Binder Sleeve 1/23], undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Chuck Connelly [From Binder Sleeve 10/23], undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Chuck Connelly [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Ceccobelli; Chia; Commandeur; Colombo [Front Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Ceccobelli; Chia; Commandeur; Colombo [Binder Sleeve 1/8], undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - [Arturo Duclos] [Front Pocket 1/2], undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - [Arturo Duclos] [Front Pocket 2/2], undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - [Arturo Duclos] [Binder Sleeve 7/7], undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Arturo Elizondo [Front Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Arturo Elizondo [Binder Sleeve 2/7], undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Arturo Elizondo [Binder Sleeve 3/7], undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Arturo Elizondo [Binder Sleeve 4/7], undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Arturo Elizondo [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Front Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Binder Sleeve 1/14], undated (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Binder Sleeve 2/14], undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Binder Sleeve 6/14], undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Binder Sleeve 10/14], undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [From Binder Sleeve 11/14], undated (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Galan [Back Pocket 3/3], undated (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Julio Galan New [Front Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Julio Galan New [Back Pocket] [1/2], undated (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Julio Galan New [Back Pocket] [2/2], undated (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Danielle Galliano [Front Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Danielle Galliano [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Vincent Gallo [Front Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Vincent Gallo [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Vincent Gallo [Loose Material], undated (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 4/14], undated (Box 34, Folder 34)